A Guide to the Records of the Chief of Staff of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1983-1994 (bulk 1990-1994)
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Governor's General Correspondence, 1990-1993., Extent: 1.35 cu. ft. (3 boxes) (Box 22-24)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Mar. 1991 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, May 1991 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, June 1991 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, July 1991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Oct.-Dec. 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Feb.-June 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, July 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Sept.-Oct. 1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Nov.-Dec. 1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1993 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-Apr. 1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, July 1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Sept.-Oct. 1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Nov.-Dec. 1993 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to the U.S. President, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Dicks, John G. III "Chips", 1989 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Jay Shropshire, Chief of Staff, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - Legislative Initiatives of the Commission on Overcrowding, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)